export const ALL_ITEMS = [
  {
    question: 'What is coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19)?',
    answer:
      'Coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) is a respiratory illness that can spread from person to person. CDC has information on COVID-19 symptoms and caring for yourself and others. COVID-19 is a new disease, caused by a novel (or new) coronavirus that has not previously been seen in humans.',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the FDA doing to respond to the COVID-19 pandemic?',
    answer:
      'The FDA, along with other federal, state, and local agencies and public health officials across the country and internationally, plays a critical role in protecting public health during the COVID-19 pandemic. FDA staff are working around the clock to support development of  medical countermeasures and are providing regulatory advice, guidance, and technical assistance to advance the development and availability of vaccines, therapies, diagnostic tests and other medical devices for use diagnosing, treating, and preventing this novel virus. The FDA continues to monitor the human and animal food supply and take swift action on fraudulent COVID-19 products.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is an emergency use authorization and how is it being used to respond to COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'In certain types of emergencies, the FDA can issue an emergency use authorization, or EUA, to provide more timely access to critical medical products that may help during the emergency when there are no adequate, approved, and available alternative options. The EUA process is different than full FDA approval, clearance, or licensing because the EUA standard requires significantly less data than otherwise would be required for approval, clearance, or licensing by the FDA. This enables the FDA to authorize the emergency use of medical products that meet the criteria for issuance within weeks rather than months to years. Under the EUA authority, the FDA evaluates requests for authorization very quickly using the evidence that is available, carefully balancing the risks and benefits of the product as we know them, in addition to evaluating other criteria. EUAs are in effect until the emergency declaration ends but can be revised or revoked as we evaluate the needs during the emergency, or as products meet the criteria to become approved, cleared, or licensed by the FDA. The What is an EUA? videoExternal Link Disclaimer provides a short summary of this information. ',
  },
  {
    question: 'How does COVID-19 spread?',
    answer:
      'COVID-19 is thought to spread mainly through close contact from person-to-person. Some people without symptoms may be able to spread the virus. We are still learning about how the virus spreads and the severity of illness it causes. The CDC has additional information on how COVID-19 spreads.',
  },
  {
    question: 'How can I prevent COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'The best way to prevent illness is to avoid being exposed to the virus. CDC recommends everyday preventive actions to help prevent the spread of respiratory diseases.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Should I wear a face covering or mask when I go out in public?',
    answer:
      'A: CDC recommends wearing masks in public when other social distancing measures are difficult to maintain (e.g., grocery stores and pharmacies) especially in areas of significant community-based transmission of the coronavirus. The purpose of wearing a mask in public is to slow the spread of the virus and help people who may have the virus and do not know it from transmitting it to others. Find more information about how to select, wear, and clean your mask. The FDA does not regulate masks or cloth face coverings worn by the general public. The FDA does regulate medical devices, including personal protective equipment (PPE) such as surgical masks and N95 respirators. PPE should be reserved for use by health care workers, first responders, and other frontline workers whose jobs put them at much greater risk of acquiring COVID-19. Read more about types of face masks and the FDA’s emergency use authorization for non-surgical face masks.',
  },
  {
    question: 'What treatments are available for COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'Currently there are no FDA-approved medicines specifically for COVID-19. However, the FDA has granted emergency use authorizations for some medicines to be used for certain patients hospitalized with COVID-19. The National Institutes of Health provides more information about treatment options.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Can I prevent or treat COVID-19 by using disinfectant sprays, wipes, or liquids on my skin? Can I inject, inhale, or ingest (swallow) disinfectants to prevent or treat COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'No. Disinfectant products such as sprays, mists, wipes, or liquids are only to be used on hard, non-porous surfaces (materials that do not absorb liquids easily) such as floors and countertops, or on soft surfaces such as mattresses, sofas, and beds.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Does spraying people with disinfectant lower the spread of COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'Currently there are no data showing that spraying people with aerosolized disinfectants, or having people walk through tunnels or rooms where disinfectant is in the air, can treat, prevent, or lower the spread of COVID-19.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Will Miracle Mineral Solution (MMS) cure COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'No. Miracle Mineral Solution does not cure COVID-19 and has not been approved by the FDA for any use. The solution, when mixed as directed, forms industrial bleach that may cause serious and potentially life-threatening side effects. FDA took action against Genesis II Church of Health and Healing for unlawfully distributing Miracle Mineral Solution for the treatment of COVID-19 and other diseases. Learn more: Danger: Don’t Drink Miracle Mineral Solution or Similar Products. ',
  },
  {
    question: 'Is hand sanitizer effective against COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'The best way to prevent the spread of infections and decrease the risk of getting sick is by washing your hands with plain soap and water, advises the CDC. Washing hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds is essential, especially after going to the bathroom; before eating; and after coughing, sneezing, or blowing one’s nose. If soap and water are not available, CDC recommends consumers use an alcohol-based hand sanitizer that contains at least 60% alcohol. ',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Where can I buy hand sanitizer? If I can’t find it in the store, can I make my own?',
    answer:
      'Many retail stores and pharmacies sell hand sanitizers. However, we understand that many stores have run out of hand sanitizers and they may be difficult to find. To help increase the availability of hand sanitizers, the FDA has issued guidance for the temporary preparation of alcohol-based hand sanitizers by some companies and pharmacies during the COVID-19 public health emergency. ',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What do I do if I get a rash or other reaction to hand sanitizer?',
    answer:
      'Call your doctor if you experience a serious reaction to hand sanitizer. The FDA encourages consumers and health care professionals to report adverse events experienced with the use of hand sanitizers to the FDA’s MedWatch Adverse Event Reporting program:',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the risk of using a hand sanitizer that contains methanol (wood alcohol) or 1-propanol?',
    answer:
      'The FDA is warning consumers and health care professionals about hand sanitizers contaminated with potentially toxic types of alcohol.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What should I do with hand sanitizer that contains methanol (wood alcohol) or 1-propanol?',
    answer:
      "If you have one of the products the FDA's do-not-use list of hand sanitizers, you should immediately stop using it and dispose of the product, ideally in a hazardous waste container. Do not pour these products down the drain or flush them. Contact your local waste management and recycling center for more information on hazardous waste disposal. Learn how to search FDA’s hand sanitizer do-not-use list, including a description of how to search for manufacturers and distributors on the label. ",
  },
  {
    question:
      'What should people do if they have been exposed to hand sanitizer with potential methanol or 1-propanol contamination?',
    answer:
      'Methanol exposure can result in nausea, vomiting, headache, blurred vision, permanent blindness, seizures, coma, permanent damage to the nervous system or death. Although people using these products on their hands are at risk for methanol poisoning, young children who accidentally swallow these products and adolescents and adults who drink these products as an alcohol (ethanol) substitute are most at risk. ',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Products online claim to prevent or treat COVID-19. Where can I report websites selling fraudulent medical products?',
    answer:
      'Currently, there are no FDA-approved products for the prevention or treatment of COVID-19. The FDA advises consumers to be cautious of websites and stores selling products that claim to prevent, treat, or cure COVID-19. If you have a question about a treatment found online, talk to your health care provider or doctor.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Am I at risk for serious complications from COVID-19 if I smoke cigarettes?',
    answer:
      'Smoking cigarettes can leave you more vulnerable to respiratory illnesses, such as COVID-19. For example, smoking is known to cause lung disease and people with underlying lung problems may have increased risk for serious complications from COVID-19, a disease that primarily attacks the lungs. Smoking cigarettes can also cause inflammation and cell damage throughout the body, and can weaken your immune system, making it less able to fight off disease. There’s never been a better time to quit smoking. If you need resources to help you quit smoking, the FDA’s Every Try Counts campaign has supportive tips and tools to help you get closer to quitting for good.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'If I vape tobacco or nicotine am I at risk for complications from COVID-19?',
    answer:
      'E-cigarette use can expose the lungs to toxic chemicals, but whether those exposures increase the risk of COVID-19 or the severity of COVID-19 outcomes is not known. However, many e-cigarette users are current or former smokers, and cigarette smoking increases the risk of respiratory infections, including pneumonia.',
  },
];
